aum-inc.com 2019-06-11

# AUM Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  
This Privacy Policy explains how American Utility Management, Inc. ("AUM", "our", or "we") collects, uses and discloses information gathered through the www.aum-inc.com web site ("Web Site"). This Privacy Policy does not cover any information collected at any other web site or offline by AUM, its affiliates or any other company (unless specifically stated). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.

Please note: Any information collected about users of the Web Site is collected and processed by AUM in the United States.

Privacy Policy

  * Effective Date
  * Acceptance and Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * Consent to Transfer:
  * Personally Identifiable Information:
  * Security:
  * Your Choices:
  * Sharing Personally Identifiable Information and Disclosure to Third Parties:
  * Web Site Usage Information and IP Addresses:
  * Changes and Additional Terms:
  * Enforcement:
  * Effective Date:

Privacy Policy  
Effective Date:  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 26, 2015. 

Acceptance and Changes to this Privacy Policy:  
By using the Web Site, you accept our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. AUM reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, by posting such change, update or modification on the Web Site. Subsequent access to the Web Site by Authorized Users may require your express consent to the revised Privacy Policy in force at that time. However, AUM will use your personally identifiable information in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time you submitted your personally identifiable information, unless you give us your consent to do otherwise.

Consent to Transfer:  
In order to administer the Web Site and conduct AUM business through the Web Site, the information you submit is collected and processed by AUM in the United States. By using the Web Site, registering with us, participating in any of our services or otherwise providing us with personally identifiable information, you consent to this transfer and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Personally Identifiable Information:  
As stated in the Terms of Use, some users may apply for access to the password-protected My AUM section of the Web Site. The password protected area is for use only by an individual who receives printed, mailed and/or electronically delivered invoices from AUM related to the amount the individual is obligated to pay for his or her residential utilities and other charges (each individual, an "Authorized User"). An Authorized User’;s access to the password protected My AUM section of the AUM web site is subject to, among other things, the Authorized User’;s acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

When an Authorized User requests access to the My AUM section of the Web Site through the registration page, he/she will be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information (information that could reasonably be used to identify you) such as e-mail address and other information that allows us to verify you as an Authorized User such as your account and statement numbers. Through AUM’s contractual relationship with an Authorized User’s place of residence (the "Residence"), the Residence has already provided AUM with other personally identifiable information found on the Authorized User’s printed invoice including the Authorized User’s name, the name of any co-residents, and Authorized User’s mailing and/or residential address and this information from Residences will be linked with the information Authorized Users provide to the Web Site.

Once the Authorized User has been granted access to the My AUM section of the Web Site and makes a decision to pay an outstanding invoice by credit or debit card, AUM will request the Authorized User’s credit or debit card number, zip code, and other verification information.

We will collect any information that you send AUM through the Web Site via our "contact us" button or other similar e-mail address or form in order to respond to your communication. We will not use the information provided to these e-mail addresses or forms for marketing purposes unrelated to your request.

AUM may also use your personally identifiable information to provide you with requested information, services or content; to verify your mailing address; to keep accurate records concerning the services you are requesting through the Web Site; for purposes disclosed to you when you provide the information or otherwise give consent; to provide you notice about or to contact you regarding any problems or questions we have about your use of the Web Site; for internal business purposes, such as to improve the Web Site and our business strategies; or to notify you of changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Use or other policy or terms that affect you and your use of the Web Site.

Security:  
No data transmission over the internet or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. However, AUM takes steps to maintain and protect the information collected through the Web Site. Please note that AUM cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to AUM, and you do so at your own risk.

Your Choices:  
Authorized Users may change their password by visiting the My Account tab of the My AUM section of the Web Site. You may request a change to your personally identifiable information by contacting AUM’s Customer Service Department, but AUM must approve those requests before they take full effect.

If an Authorized User’s authorization to access the password protected section of the Web Site ends for any reason, including a request by the Authorized User to terminate the account, for security reasons we will retain the Authorized User’s account information and information regarding the Authorized User’s use of the Web Site.

Sharing Personally Identifiable Information and Disclosure to Third Parties:  
AUM may transfer, disclose and share information collected from or about Authorized Users with its related companies, the Authorized User’s Residence and AUM’s vendors for the purposes of conducting business with Authorized Users, processing payments authorized by an Authorized User, and administering the Web Site.

Unless otherwise prohibited by law, AUM may process, transfer or disclose information about its users, including personally identifiable information, and may use IP addresses to identify users in cooperation with internet service providers or law enforcement agencies, to comply with a legal obligation, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the Web Site and applicable laws, or to protect the legal rights, interests, or safety of the Web Site, Authorized Users or others.

Additionally, you consent to AUM processing, disclosing and transferring user information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation or restructuring, the sale of substantially all of its assets, or other fundamental corporate change, unless otherwise prohibited by law.

AUM does not share any personally identifiable information it collects from the Web Site with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. However, AUM does not control any Residence’s use of personally identifiable information that the Residence obtains from or about an Authorized User.

Cookies:  
Cookies are pieces of information that a web site either transfers to your computer’s hard drive or stores temporarily in your computer’s memory for record-keeping purposes. We may use cookies for a number of purposes, such as tracking usage patterns on the Web Site, facilitating the transmission of a communication, customizing your experience on the Web Site, facilitating your ability to navigate the Site and as part of a verification or screening process. The Web Site does not save personally identifiable information in cookies, but each cookie contains a unique identification number, logged by our web server, that tracks a user’s actions through the Web Site. In the case of Authorized Users, these cookies are linked in our database(s) to your identity (your personally identifiable information) by our web servers.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent by indicating this in the preferences or options menu in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of this Web Site will not operate correctly if you disable cookies and you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features of this Site. You should consult with your browser’s provider/manufacturer if you have any questions regarding disabling cookies.

Web Site Usage Information and IP Addresses:  
When your computer contacts our web servers (for example, when you visit the Web Site), our web servers automatically may collect non-personally identifiable information ("NPII") including Web Site usage information, which is information that describes how visitors use and navigate the Web Site, such as the date and time of access, the web page you visit immediately preceding and immediately following your visit to the Web Site, the type of web browser and computer operating system you are using, and your IP address (a number that is assigned to your computer or network when you are on the Internet). AUM may disclose NPII to third parties. We use NPII for internal purposes, such as system administration, to analyze web site usage, to make your use of the Web Site more efficient, and to audit the use of the Web Site. AUM may link NPII to an Authorized User’s personally identifiable information for security and internal purposes. If you feel that we are not abiding by this Privacy Policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800-418-5393 or via email at [customerservice@aum-inc.com](mailto:customerservice@aum-inc.com).
